<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE ProductManagementData SYSTEM "ProductManagementData.dtd">
<ProductManagementData creationDate="20051124110445">
<ProviderInfo>
<ProviderId>IMS Nagra</ProviderId>
<ProviderName>IMS Nagravision S.A.</ProviderName>
<DtdVersion>1.1.1</DtdVersion>
</ProviderInfo>
<ProductChangeNotification>

<ProductData>
<Product>
<ProductId>18759</ProductId>
<ProductType productKind="PPV" impulsiveFlag="1" specialPpv="0"/>
<ProductStatus suspendedFlag="0" soldFlag="0"/>
<ProductText language="eng">
<ProductName>桃色風雲--搖擺狗</ProductName>
<ProductDescription>桃色風雲--搖擺狗</ProductDescription>
</ProductText>
<SalePeriod beginTime="20051126220000" endTime="20051127221000"/>
<ProductCategory>3</ProductCategory>
<EpgPrice moneyUnit="TWD">50</EpgPrice>
<PpvData>
<ValidityPeriod beginTime="20051126000000" endTime="20051129000000"/>
<Event beginTime="20051127220000" duration="3600">
<EventId>L00000034598</EventId>
<PreviewTime>3</PreviewTime>
<EpgText language="chi">
<Name>桃色風雲--搖擺狗</Name>
<Description>美國總統鬧出性醜聞，面對著醜聞成為頭條新聞的壓力，及兩週後的總統大選，白宮這回該怎麼做呢？簡單，發動一場戰爭！白宮危機處理專家康洛德（勞勃狄尼洛，「老大靠邊閃」）受命替總統解圍，轉移民眾注意力，於是他找來了好萊塢大製片家史丹利（達斯汀霍夫曼，「地動天驚」、「雨人」），虛擬一場在阿爾巴尼亞的戰爭，但這場戰爭不是發生在真實的戰場，而是在攝影棚當中，不用任何真槍實彈，他們製造各種有關戰爭的新聞片段，甚至趁機推出愛國歌曲大撈一筆。起初一切都進行地很順利，廣大民眾的心，隨著真真假假的戰爭新聞而起伏，但不久後卻漏洞百出，假的戰區英雄意外死亡，製片史丹利為了居功而不願保密，中情局也開始懷疑這場美國總統的桃色風雲該如何圓滿收場？導演巴瑞李文遜曾以「雨人」、「早安越南」、「豪情四兄弟」等片獲得空前的成功。</Description>
</EpgText>
<EpgText language="eng">
<Name>Wag The Dog</Name>
<Description>What do the President’s advisers do when a sex scandal threatens to explode across front pages nationwide, with the election is only 14 days away? Simple. Start a war! Faced with this dilemma, a ‘spin-doctor’ (DeNiro, Men Of Honor, Meet The Parents, The Adventures of Rocky &amp; Bullwinkle ) is called in to fabricate a nonexistent war for the President to win, and to distract the American public. Wars are no longer fought on battlefields but on TV, so naturally a hotshot Hollywood producer (Hoffman, Being John Malcovich, Cosm) is hired to manufacture a war in distant Albania — without a shot being fired. With its first-class cast and ascerbic humour, Wag the Dog is a biting satire that has never been more appropriate.</Description>
</EpgText>
<ParentalRating>3</ParentalRating>
<DvbContent>
<Content nibble1="1" nibble2="0"/>
<User nibble1="0" nibble2="0"/>
</DvbContent>
<ChannelNumber>503</ChannelNumber>
</Event>
</PpvData>
</Product>
</ProductData>
</ProductChangeNotification>
</ProductManagementData>
